PHAM DUY MINH

WEB DEVELOPER



- **2** 033 345 4717
- duyminh081201@gmail.com
- 2 102/25 Tô Hiến Thành, Q.10, HCM
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/minhdp
- https://duyminh.tech

PROFILE

I graduated with a major in software engineering at Ho Chi Minh City University of Education. I have a passion for web programming. I have experience working with Front End frameworks and libraries such as ReactJS, Angular, Ant Design, MUI, Bootstrap, Tailwind. In addition, I also have experience working with Back End using Python, PostgreSQL, REST API.

SKILLS

FRONT END

- HTML, CSS, JS
- · Ant Design, Bootstrap, MUI, Tailwind
- Web Responsive, Web Design
- ReactJS, AngularJS

BACK END

- Pvthon, NodeJS, Fast API
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQL Server
- REST API
- Data Structures and Algorithms

TOOLS

- Git, Github, Gitlab
- Figma, Photoshop
- Jira Scrum

EXPERIENCE



EduplaX · Front End Web

6/2022 - 12/2022

- Use reactjs and nextjs to build Eduplax educational products
- Build websites according to the UI/UX designer's design on Figma
- Make responsive on different devices
- Integrate API into website
- Work together with the backend team to build APIs
- Fix errors related to website interface and features



TMA Solution · Internship

3/2023 - 5/2023

- Build websites according to mentor's request using Angular
- Fix errors related to interface and functionality
- Make daily work progress reports

EDUCATION

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

Software Engineering

2019 - 2023

GPA: 3.47

Degree classification: Very good

CERTIFICATE

COMPLETE AGILE SCRUM PROJECT MANAGEMENT USING JIRA TOOL



Udemy https://udemy.com/certificate/UC-3af1b756-

Apr/2022 <u>5249-4102-ae6c-154074dd75b2/</u>

ANGULAR - THE COMPLETE GUIDE



Udemy <u>https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-</u>

Aug/2023 75ded710-eeaa-4577-bb4d-22d1f976ab37/